## **KAHO SHIBUYA**

# Frontend Developer React Developer

6	https://kahoshibuya.dev/
i	<b>n</b> https://www.linkedin.com/in/kaho-shibuya/
(	https://github.com/shiv-chan
5	kshibuya31@gmail.com
	604-499-7851

Aspiring frontend developer with a specialization in React development. A highly passionate learner and have worked on 5+ personal projects. With 3+ years of experience as a digital marketer, I value user experience, promoting, and monetizing web services. My professional background enables me to develop optimal frontend applications by enhancing collaboration with the marketing and business teams and seeing the product from a business standpoint.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Puppy Time Vancouver - Web Designer & Web Developer

Apr 2021 - Aug 2021

- Designed and developed the website from scratch including the page structure, theme, and UI/UX, which increased their brand awareness and achieved new clients.
- Collaborated with the marketing team and created the website SEO strategy-wise.
- Used: Squarespace, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Figma

### sann, Inc. - Online Advertising Operation

Oct 2019 - Dec 2020

- Supported sales team with building ad campaign strategies by analyzing clients' past performances such as CPM or CPC or marketing trend data.
- Reported the results and suggested the next actions to the clients, which led to continuous contracts and incremental revenues.
- $^{\circ}$  Created tools that reduced human-errors by  $\sim 90\%$  and automated repetitive duties with Google products such as Spreadsheets or App Script.
- Used: JavaScript (Google App Script)

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

#### Go-to Pomodoro

- https://go-to-pomodoro.vercel.app/
- https://github.com/shiv-chan/go-to-pomodoro
- Built a responsive web app that the user can customize her/his own pomodoro timer with favourite BGM playing by embedded YouTube video player.
- Created a timer with minimal time logging.
- Composed Styled Components to change the theme colour according to its session.
- Used: React, Redux, IFrame Player API, Styled Component, Material UI, Figma

### Weather App

- https://react-weather-app-peach-mu.vercel.app/
- https://github.com/shiv-chan/react-weather-app
- Implemented code with both Context API and Redux to see the difference.
- Fetched data from API asynchronously with passing a query using createAsyncThunk.
- Used: React, Redux, Open Weather API, Sass

### **EDUCATION**

### Cornerstone International Community College of Canada

Diploma, Web and Mobile App Development

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

• Related courses: Computing, Algorithms, Problem-solving, OOP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js

### **Sprott Shaw College**

Diploma, Business Admin Sales & Digital Marketing with Honours Feb 2015 - Jan 2016 | GPA 4.14

- Related courses: Bookkeeping, Accounting, Customer Services, Web design, SEO
- Practicum at Okanagan Boys and Girls Clubs as Digital Marketing Assistant